(Leonard:)Well, Vegas, but...
(Sheldon:)Ugh, Atlantic City
without the taffy?
(Sheldon:)No, thank you.
(Leonard:)That's fine, 'cause actually
you're not invited.
(Sheldon:)Well, now...
well, that's hurtful.
(Penny:)Oh, Sheldon, you don't
even like it there.
(Sheldon:)I can consider a place
(Sheldon:)America's urinal cake
(Sheldon:)and still enjoy
the occasional visit.
(Leonard:)Not this time.
(Sheldon:)Oh, fine. Then I'll just
hang out with Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)He's coming, too.
Well, then Raj and I will...
(Leonard:)Nope.
Very well. Stuart.
(Leonard:)Oh, great. Do that.
(Sheldon:)Ugh. Stuart.
(Amy(on Skype):)Hi, Sheldon. What's new?
(Sheldon:)Our friends are jerks,
and I'm mad at all of them.
I said, “What's new?” but sure.
(Sheldon:)Can you believe
they planned a trip
(Sheldon:)to Las Vegas
and didn't invite me?
(Amy:)Did you refuse to apologize
(Amy:)and act like they were stupid
for being mad?
(Sheldon:)You know, I liked it better
when there was still
(Sheldon:)a little mystery left
in our relationship.
(Amy:)Everyone tried
to take care of you,
(Amy:)and you were nothing
but mean to them.